<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yuan Ho</title>
    <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yuan Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:49:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yuan-ho.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>4G LTE-Advanced Pro and The Road to 5G</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/4g/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:49:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/4g/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction to LTE</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/lte_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 10:08:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/lte_intro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/11/10/my-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:50:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/11/10/my-cv/</guid>
      <description>RESEARCH INTERESTS  Natural language processing Data mining Machine learning  &amp;nbsp;
EDUCATION Graduate Institute of Communication Engineering, National Taiwan University Taipei, Taiwan
Sep. 2001 – Jun. 2003
 Degree: Master of Science Master’s thesis: “An Initial Study on Automatic Summarization of Chinese Spoken Documents” Supervisor: Professor Lin-Shan Lee Average: 90.94 / 100; ranking: 13th / 87  Department of Electrical Engineering, National Taiwan University Taipei, Taiwan
Sep. 1996 – Jun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Finland</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/07/15/trip-to-finland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 13:11:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/07/15/trip-to-finland/</guid>
      <description>April 2018, 2 colleagues and I were sent to Oulu, Finland by MediaTek to have a 10-days co-working with the L1 people of the company&amp;rsquo;s branch in Finland. The team&amp;rsquo;s people are mostly former employees of Nokia. The subject was partition discussion of the new 5G modem project. We had a great time during the visit, knowing each other, discussing technical topics, exchanging thoughts, etc.. They are excellent engineers.
The Finland colleagues spoke frankly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Methods for Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 14:15:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/nlp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My seat at MediaTek</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/06/28/my-seat-at-mtk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 10:24:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2019/06/28/my-seat-at-mtk/</guid>
      <description>July, 2019, the new building of MediaTek is completed and all software teams and some firmware teams of the cellular modem project are moving into it. The new building is only about 80 meters away from the previous one. This picture was taken right before moving. The job is the same, just new seat and office furnitures.
It is an amazing trip that I have the opprtunity to join the development from 2G to 5G modems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/deep_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 23:41:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/docs/deep_learning/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local News Promotional</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2018/05/01/local-news-promotional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 21:52:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/blog/2018/05/01/local-news-promotional/</guid>
      <description>May, 2019, MediaTek decided to promote the company&amp;rsquo;s recent achievements in 5G development. In the meantime, one local TV News wants to have more reports on Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s high-tech firms. Therefore, this News clip.
The rightmost person with left hand half-raised is me. I was holding a cross-site meeting with Finland colleagues. Everybody was laughing because the cameraman asked us to do some actions (give him a shot). Apparently, we didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://yuan-ho.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuan-ho.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>